<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome to CEDA! on Hinode site on GH pages</title><link>https://mjpritchard.github.io/my-hinode-site-hugo/en/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome to CEDA! on Hinode site on GH pages</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright © 2023 Mark Dumay.</copyright><atom:link href="https://mjpritchard.github.io/my-hinode-site-hugo/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Status</title><link>https://mjpritchard.github.io/my-hinode-site-hugo/en/status/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjpritchard.github.io/my-hinode-site-hugo/en/status/</guid><description>This webpage provides information about current and future incidents related to CEDA and JASMIN services.
You may also wish to check our news feed for recent updates.
## Status key
Status Description Down Affected services completely unavailable Degraded Some services unavailable, either completely or not working to their full ability At risk Affected services available, but at significant risk of outage Normal Normal service Current status Status Services affected Updates All CEDA Archive and JASMIN services No current updates Future incidents Date of incident Status Services affected Updates 23rd October 2023 for up to two weeks All CEDA Archive and JASMIN service.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://mjpritchard.github.io/my-hinode-site-hugo/en/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjpritchard.github.io/my-hinode-site-hugo/en/about/</guid><description>Bootstrap framework Build fast, responsive sites with Bootstrap 5. Easily customize your site with the source Sass files.
Full text search Search your site with FlexSearch, a full-text search library with zero dependencies.
Development tools Use Node Package Manager to automate the build process and to keep track of dependencies.
Additional features include:
Switching between light mode and dark mode Support for multiple languages Reusable Bootstrap components through configurable shortcodes and partials Versioned documentation, including sidebar navigation and version switcher Embedded comments through light-weight integration with GitHub via utteranc.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://mjpritchard.github.io/my-hinode-site-hugo/browserconfig.xml</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjpritchard.github.io/my-hinode-site-hugo/browserconfig.xml</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>